Congratulations,
fellow citizens!
3023 will go down in history
as the year we
triumphed over COVID-19!
We interrupt
the triumph over COVID-19
for a special report.
A new virus...
- Oh, for Pete's sake.
- A new virus dubbed EXPLOVID-23
has broken out among the mutants
who dwell beneath New New York.
- Symptoms include blinding,
uncontrollable anger!
As well as a mild cough,
which I don't have. I'm fine.
- A complete travel ban
to and from the sewers
is being enforced by the
city's fattest police officers.
Bye, Mom! Bye, Dad! Love ya!
- Feh. Always with the love.
- We already hugged you.
Now, we gotta talk about it?
- Sorry I'm late. What?
- Let's move, you sofa
snails! We've got a delivery!
And now, I'm
proud to present
the city's highest award,
the key to the Times
Square liquor cabinet,
to the super-spreader
of truth himself,
Bill Nye, the Science Head!
- Congratulations, Mr. Science.
Let me just bend that
mic for you.
- Thank you for this
tremendously dubious honor.
After what seemed like a
thousand years of COVID...
- But was actually more!
- I declare the pandemic
to be officially over.
- Ugh. Watch where
ya's coughin', bow tie!
Ow-zers!
- For crying out loud!
I'm using the principles
of aerodynamics
to get the hell outta here!
Do it again!
- An anger pandemic?
Not to point fingers,
but Leela's spreading it.
I am not, you jerks!
I'm just running a couple
degrees angrier than normal.
- Good news, infecter-inos!
I've developed a test to
see who's got the virus
and who's just naturally mean.
You simply jam this
Q-tip up your nose...
way,
way up your nose,
and collect a brain
matter sample.
- That looks kinda fun.
I can't wait to do
it hundreds of times!
- Now, we wait for a line to
appear under the two control dots.
If the line curves
up, you're fine.
Huzzah!
Here goes nothin'.
- This can't be
right, Professor!
Your test stinks, and
so does your ugly face!
- Oh no! She's got it!
- Quarantine her
in the angry dome!
- Stupid, stinkin', lousy,
no good, son of a...
- While we don't yet know
how the virus spreads,
we do know it's anger-based.
I am therefore issuing
an executive aroo
that everyone wear a
mask over their ears
to prevent the transmission
of upsetting remarks.
Agnew! Come!
- Mr. President, how could this
possibly be of the slightest...
- Thanks, fellas. Since I
don't hear any questions,
this prrress conference
is adjourned!
- Out of an
abundance of caution,
all work will
henceforth go remote
using a new app called Gloom.
In some ways, it will be better.
Especially for those
of us with families.
- Dwight, stop Gloom-bombing
your dad's meeting!
And put on some britches!
- Hey, LaBarbara. How's
your grandma? She improvin'?
- Yeah, she doin' alright.
Give her my best.
I'm having
trouble with my... Anybody hear...
- Wi-Fi issues...
- hungry.
Bender, you idiot!
Do you have to eat those now?!
- I don't have to
eat anything ever.
- I'm warning you!
What
are you gonna do?
Hi... yah!
- Wow, this technology's
come a long way.
- I actually like
working on Gloom.
These hair filters
save a ton of time.
- Uh-wha...
- Professor, you're a teddy bear!
I assure you I am not.
Aw...
- Is this the Gloom room where
I can refill my prescriptions?
- No! This is a
delivery company!
- Can you deliver
my prescriptions?
- We could, but we won't!
Oh, this is a dismal failure.
Everyone report to
the office in person.
- But, Professor! That is a violation
of health and safety standards.
- Everything we do is a violation
of health and safety standards!
Just wear a mask!
We are dealing with
a highly contagious virus,
so we'll need to
practice hygiene theater.
You know, I heard there's
not really even a virus at all.
It's just a big hoax,
like the moon landing.
- You were on the
moon last week!
You grew up on Mars!
That's what they
want you to think!
Ugh. Enough with the
conspiracy theories, people!
Let's look at the facts.
Irrational rage,
spread through saliva and spit,
constant angry moaning.
It's all the classic symptoms...
of zombie-ism!
No way!
- That's completely unscientific,
Hermes. EXPLOVID victims
move at way too normal
a speed to be zombies.
There are all
speeds of zombies out there!
Fast ones. Slow ones.
Brisk shufflers.
But the cure is always the same.
Voodoo.
- Balderdash!
People stopped believing in
voodoo back in Fry's time.
But voodoo didn't
stop believing in them.
Voodoo may not be
well understood,
but it gets results.
- You know what
else gets results?
Public ridicule.
And yet, there are zombies.
Oh shoot.
I forgot to pick up a goat!
Dwight, go across the hall and
borrow goat from Mrs. Wilson.
- Pack your bags. We are
going to New New Orleans.
For Mardi Gras?
- No. Well, I mean,
it happens to be Mardi Gras,
but that's beside the point!
I believe there are people there
who could defeat
this virus with...
voodoo.
Dwight, go to your room right now!
You are messin' with powers
you don't understand, husband.
But I do!
- Then come with me, woman!
- You must listen to me
'cause I grew up
in a voodoo family,
and zombie-ism killed my father!
Then brought him back to life!
Me don't want anymore
to do with that world.
- Then I'll have to seek out
these practitioners of
the dark arts on my own.
Hopefully, they are near that
place with the good beignets.
- Be very careful, husband,
and promise me one thing.
If you survive,
you gonna bring me back
some of them beignets!
- What? It's my
emotional support gun.
- Which section, sir?
Business or fighting?
- Uh, the first one.
- Right this way.
- Hand sanitizer?
- No thanks.
- Eh, more for me.
Ma'am? Ma'am?
Please, don't jam your
husband into the overhead bin.
- Don't you tell my wife
how to jam me into things!
- I know my rights.
I'm recording you!
- And I'm recording you for
recording him without permission!
- As your mayor, I'm
proud to announce
that our city's most
prominent egghead
has developed a
vaccine that will end
my terrible poll numbers
once and for all!
- Quite so.
Thanks to cutting-edge
RNA technology,
my vaccine is as potent
as it is untested.
- Ha! My essentially
identical vaccine
is far superior!
- Wernstrom.
- It's a two-shot regimen.
- Oh, yeah?
Well, mine's three, and it makes
your shoulder sore for a month!
- Mine makes your arm
shrivel and fall off!
- Big deal! Mine comes
with a futuristic way
of knowing exactly who's been
vaccinated and who hasn't,
a small scrap of easily
lost paper.
- I made your favorite, Leela.
Chicken-shaped steak!
"Wow, this is great, Fry!"
Is what I'd say if this
pan sauce weren't so bland!
- Yeah, well, I know that's
just the virus talking.
How's the cream pie?
- Scoop Chang, New New Yorker Crossword
Puzzle editor, Smartwatch Edition.
Dr. Wernstrom, what
do you say to reports
your vaccine has the
side effect of magnetism?
That's a feature, not a bug.
- Linda, Morbo and Linda.
According to an
anonymous internet post,
your anti-anger vaccine
causes sterility.
Care to comment?
- The sterility is essential!
Studies show that kids are
what make people angriest!
Everyone hates kids!
- Am I the only journalist here
who even bothered to
bring my own facts?
- Dr. Banjo!
- Yes, the Dr. Banjo
of The Dr. Banjo Experience
Podcast Experience Hour.
Professor Farnsworth, how do you
respond to rumors I'm starting
that there are 5G
chips in your vaccine?
- I would simply reassure you
that the 5G chips are safe
and purely for
surveillance purposes.
Dear God!
- But that's how it works!
The 5G chips track
the virus particles,
so the space lasers
can shoot them.
Keep that quackery away from me!
- May I take your tray, ma'am?
- No, you may not
take my dang tray!
- Ow! Why do we have
to serve shish kabob?
Hey, don't make me come back there!
- Sir, please go back to your seat.
- I'm the captain!
- Don't you pull
rank with me, flyboy!
Sit your tushy down,
and drive this thing.
- Tushy my ass!
This
is the captain speaking.
Passengers fighting in the
window seats will notice
we're careening past
scenic Lake Pontchartrain.
- Help... I can't
move my legs...
Ooh! I smell gumbo!
Hello, madam. Is
this the Voodoo HQ?
- Shh. You do voodoo?
- You misconstrue.
Who do voodoo at the HQ?
- Entendu.
But such information
won't come cheap.
- I found this quarter outside.
Don't worry. I wiped
off most of the vomit.
- Then let us consult the tarot.
The Key of Bones,
the Hanging Man,
the Man Being Crushed
by a Big Beignet,
and the Man Being Beaten
by the Saints Mascot.
Which path do you choose?
- Hm.
What's in that pot
under the hanging guy?
- Boiling gumbo.
- I'll start with the gumbo.
Hit me.
Bam!
- Mm. Kinda mild.
Guess I'll try this one instead.
- This damned
pandemic would be over
if only people would
take my vaccine.
Why is everyone
but me so stupid?!
- Splah. Because everyone
but you uses social media!
These vaccine fascists
are taking away our freedom!
I might as well be
in a cage at the zoo,
like my aunt!
- This confounded mask
is destroying my lungs.
All this
misinformation on Facebag
is tearing us apart.
I wonder who's posting it.
- What else should I post, Dad?
- Who cares? The
crazier the better.
Tell 'em worm medicine
helps!
Those poor, easily
manipulated fools.
Soon, our time to
invade will draw near!
- Sounds fun.
I'll pack my
scream-canceling headphones.
Lousy,
rotten, tiny angry dome!
- Leela? I'm really sorry.
I tried shoving these
flowers where you said,
but I just couldn't manage it.
Please take them.
- Don't come any
closer, you dope!
You'll get sick and
probably beat up.
- I don't care. I can't
stand being apart any longer!
I'm coming in.
- That fortune teller must
have been jerking my chicken!
There's nothing
here!
- Nothing but us bones, mon ami.
- Sweet andouille of St. Louis!
A robot made of bones!
- Je m'appelle Bonebot.
Been bones-keepin' this boneyard
for three bone-dred years.
- Oh good! Because I am
on a bone-related errand.
I'm looking for a secret
bone key to the Voodoo HQ.
- Huh. I ain't never
seen no bone key.
- Have you checked that
prominently displayed skull?
- Well, huh. Guess I never really
done looked 'round the place.
Probably 'cause I got no eyes.
Come on! I'll give you a ride.
Go on and git from
here, gar fish!
- That eighth bowl of gumbo
may have been a mistake.
- No amount of gumbo's
a mistake, mon ami.
Water's always choppy
in there here parts
on account of the
force field levees.
- Y'all see a dugong
from Macon, run him down!
He absconded with
my daughter's dowry.
- This place gimme
the heebie-jeebies,
and not the boogie-woogie kind!
- You're literally
made of bones!
- And I aim to keep it that way!
Bon voyage!
- Wh-Who goes there?
Barbados Slim?!
- People Magazine's
Sexiest Man Alive.
Come in, Hermes!
Make yourself feel inadequate.
Tonight, Earth
is under attack.
Alien invaders have taken advantage
of our planet's internal divisions
to launch an all-out
assault.
Die, you disgusting
freak!
I just hope I kill
you before those invaders do.
- All hope is lost. Morbo?
- They must be destroyed!
Both sides must be destroyed!
- I am so sick of you!
Help!
- You're the head
of the Voodoo HQ?
I can't believe it!
- Believe it, man.
Me studied with the
best of the best.
She goes by the name of...
LaBarbara.
And she was good at voodoo, too.
- You stay away from her!
She's married to me now!
You two are mostly
ancient history.
- History has a way of
repeating itself, brother.
Now, what brings you here?
- The virus. I believe voodoo
might be the only thing
that can fight it.
- Well, that much is obvious.
I thought it might be a
form of demonic possession,
but the tests came
back negative.
- But consider this.
My theory is the virus
is a type of zombie-ism!
- Sweet potatoes of Barbados!
You don't see a lot of
angry, shouting zombies,
but it would explain a lot.
Hermes, you may have
cracked this coconut.
- Stop naming foods!
Gettin' hungry again.
- Sadly, curing zombie-ism
is the kind of voodoo
I don't do.
There's only one person
with that expertise,
and I'm afraid...
- Afraid she might be too sexually
attracted to you to think straight?
Well,
you're mostly right.
- LaBarbara?!
- Hermes, I couldn't
let you do this alone.
You were brave to come
here, and I love you.
Well, hello, Barbados.
- But, how did you find us here?
And why do you have a
key to Barbados' place?
- Eh, that's not important.
- I've also got a
key to your place.
- Also not important.
- Come! Follow me to
the inner sanctum.
What dark,
well-lit sorcery is this?
- People of Earth! I am Lrrr,
ruler of the planet
Omicron Persei 8!
Excuse me.
I shall rule mercilessly
over your weak and divided...
That's odd. I've
never sneezed before.
I don't even have a nose.
Me neither.
- Stop interrupting me while I'm
trying to dominate these people!
- You couldn't dominate
a bowl of fudge!
Although you sure try!
- Oh yeah?
- Oh!
- It's better than that
flavor-free dessert
- that you serve.
- Is that right?
Oh, it's
just as I feared.
The virus has mutated
with Omicronium NDNDNA.
It's a highly contagious
Omicron variant.
- You're a contagious variant!
- Go back where you came
from, you Omi-clods.
Everyone is so angry.
Especially me!
- Ow! My schnookus!
- Kill all humans!
Kill all humans!
- Can robots even get the virus?
What virus?
- Now, the key is to
produce a voodoo potion
that tricks the body into
thinking it has the virus,
but without actually
gettin' the disease.
- Aha! So, the immune
system falls under its spell
and produces anti-jujus that
attack the spike protein,
thus inoculating against
future infection.
- Precisely.
You got some serious
mental pecs, husband.
My second favorite kind.
- Hey, cut that out!
Why didn't I get a wink
for my mental pecs?
- Now, we gonna need
an animal sacrifice.
I-I mean, um, test subject.
- Not me.
- I'm too angry!
- Don't worry, man.
The doll won't feel a thing.
- Ow! My calculator arm!
I just hope
it's got the mojo
to defeat this anger virus.
Come, let's run a test.
- Hm. I just feel a normal,
easy-to-repress rage.
- Then, perhaps we should
test it a bit more thoroughly.
- That's enough testing!
Voodoo shots!
Freshly conjured voodoo shots!
Ow!
- Can you assure me
there is absolutely
no science in this vaccine?
- Nothing but 100%
Louisiana swamp voodoo.
Ouchie!
I was, uh, promised a lollipop.
Uh, here.
Mm, tastes a bit
like wig glue.
What a bunch of mumbo gumbo!
Anything I can't
understand is fake!
Ooh!
Tense
peaceful
Ahh, that's better.
Hermes, my friend.
I owe you an apology for
being so anti-voodoo.
It may seem bat-whack
crazy to a layman,
but I see now that
voodoo methods
are built on centuries
of brilliant scholarship.
- It's okay, Professor.
And it's understandable.
After all, any
sufficiently advanced magic
is indistinguishable
from science.
- Ahh yeah...
uplifting